事件はまだ　続いてるっていうのに
The case isn't over yet.
私たちはもうドローンに頼ってる
And we're already
relying on Drones.
これだよ　これ
This is awesome!
Games should be real after all.
やっぱり　ゲームはリアルじゃなきゃ
公安局です
MWPSB!
Hinakawa!
雛河！
「犯罪係数　１３３」
Crime Coefficient is 133.
He is a target for enforcement action.
「執行対象です」
I-I'm going to administer justice!
し…執行です
次のエリアストレス警報
The next Area Stress warning was issued
in the commercial area 8 km ahead of here!
ここから８ｋｍ先の商業エリアです
あ　もう　切りがない
Give me a break!
There's no end to this!
スキャナーに監視された　この社会で
In a society monitored by scanners,
you can't pretend to be someone else.
他人に成り済ますことは　不可能だ
That all changes, though,
ただし　意図してクリアなサイコパスを維持できるなら
if the person is able to keep
their Psycho-Pass clear intentionally.
話は変わってくる
For example,
organ transplants.
例えば　臓器移植だ
多くを取り換えることは　サイコパスの移植に等しい
Transplanting a lot of one's organs
is like transplanting one's Psycho-Pass.
If the Psycho-Pass is clear,
クリアな人間であれば
the discrepancy would probably
be treated as a margin of error.
誤差の範囲で　処理されちまうだろうからな
鹿矛囲の隠れ家には　大量の臓器が保管してあったそうだ
I heard that lots of organs
were stored in Kamui's hideout.
増田先生　お迎えに上がりました
Representative Masuda,
I came to get you.
お前と同じように　他人に成り済ました人間がいる
Just like you, there are people
who're pretending to be someone else.
そいつらが鹿矛囲の仲間か
Are they Kamui's accomplices?
Inspector.
監視官
また　撃てませんでした
I couldn't shoot again.
But if it weren't for you,
we would've all been dead.
しかし　あなたがいなければわれわれは全滅していた
Most importantly, we were able
to come face-to-face with the ghost.
何より　透明人間の目前までたどりついた
やはり　鹿矛囲を逮捕できるのは
You're the only one
who can arrest Kamui after all.
あなただけだ
奪われ続けるなら
If I keep having things taken away from me, I'm gonna lose my mind
Ubaware tsuzukeru nara mou kurutte shimau yo
奪われ続けるなら
もう狂ってしまうよ
This endless "end" will make me stop breathing
Owari no nai "owari" ni boku wa iki wo shinaku natte
終わりの無い「終わり」に僕は息をしなくなって
Enigmatic Feeling
Enigmatic feeling
Why do they have to take things away from me? I'm about to fall apart
Ubawanakya ikenai no? Mou hodokete shimau yo
奪わなきゃいけないの
もうほどけてしまうよ
世界が溶け出して
The world began to melt
Sekai ga tokedashite
もうほどけてしまうよ
世界が溶け出して
God descended to confront and ask me
Kami-sama ga orite kite boku ni tsukitsuketa
神様が降りて来て
僕に突きつけた
"Who are you?"
Who are you?
I freed myself by walking in the divide of this world broken into two
Futatsu ni wakareta sekai ni sotte jibun wo hanatta
２つに分かれた世界に沿って
自分を放った
Is there only one God in such a fine borderline?
Kamihitoe darou kamihitoe darou kyoukaisen kami wa hitori na no?
紙一重だろう　紙一重だろう
境界線　神は１人なの
I'm gonna lose my mind, I'm gonna lose my mind...
Okashiku natte okashiku natte
おかしくなって おかしくなって
Suddenly I'll find myself taking you away
Fui ni kimi wo ubatte shimau no darou
ふいに君を奪ってしまうのだろう
Crazy! Crazy!
Crazy Crazy　完全浮遊体
I'm completely adrift
Kanzen fuyuutai
Crazy Crazy　完全浮遊体
Because my heart can't focus
Pinto no awanai kokoro ni
ピントの合わない心に
Shake me! Shake me!
Shake me Shake me　完全浮遊体
I'm completely adrift
Kanzen fuyuutai
Shake me Shake me　完全浮遊体
I can't even look into the mirror
Kagami sae mo nozokenai
鏡さえも覗けない
#7: Untraceable Children
He tried to see if an unauthorized person
can carry a Dominator.
適正を持たない人間が　ドミネーターを所持できるか試した
That was the first incident.
それが第１の事件
ドミネーターで監視官を裁けるのか知ろうとした
He then tried to see if a Dominator
can judge Inspectors.
That was the second one.
第２の事件
This time, he attacked the MWPSB
and obtained multiple Dominators.
そして今回　公安を襲い　複数のドミネーターを手に入れた
おそらく　仲間に与えるため
He probably did it
to give them to his accomplices.
In other words, his goal
cannot be achieved by himself.
つまり　鹿矛囲の目的は　１人では成し得ないということ
手に入れたドミネーターを　いったい　誰に向けようとしているの？
Who on earth are you trying
to point those Dominators at?
そしてあなたは裁かれるどころか
And, Dominators can't even
recognize you, much less judge you.
ドミネーターに認識すらされない
Why on earth is that?
いったい　なぜ？
When something impossible happens,
there are only two possibilities.
あり得ない事態が起こったなら
疑うべきは　２つだけだ
前提条件が間違っているか
Either your assumptions are wrong,
or you have gone crazy.
それとも　あんたの頭がいかれちまったか
It would make more sense
if this was just a figment of my imagination.
私だけが　虚構にとらわれているなら　分かる
But that's not the case here.
Kamui's existence is an unmistakable fact.
でも　そうじゃない
鹿矛囲の存在はもう　疑いようがない事実
But Dominators don't
even recognize him.
だが　ドミネーターは認識すらしない
He's also different
from Makishima.
槙島とも　また違う
He's unique, but not
criminally asymptomatic?
免罪体質とも違う　特殊な体質？
だから　この社会に認識されない…
That's why he's not
recognized in this society.
But there should
definitely be a trick there...
しかし　そこには必ず仕掛けがあるはずだ
...a significant trick that takes advantage
of some shortcoming in this society
個人を徹底的に管理するこの社会の隙間をついた　重大な仕掛けが…
that thoroughly
manages each individual.
The...
それは…
The answer may be
closer than we think.
それは…
案外　近い所に…
転がっているのかもしれない
What?
Is something wrong?
どうかしましたか
Oh, sorry.
I spaced out a bit.
ごめんなさい　少しぼーっとしてて
What did you just say?
今　何て？
I was talking about Kamui.
鹿矛囲です
I think uncovering his bodily constitution,
which isn't recognized by cymatic scans,
サイマティックスキャンに認識されない　やつの体質を暴くことが
is the best way to resolve
this whole thing.
事件解決の最善手ではないかと
Yes. If we just figure out that reason,
we might be able to determine his color.
ええ　その理由さえ分かれば
彼に色をつけられるかもしれない
なぜ　鹿矛囲が透明人間でいられるか
How can Kamui
continue to be a ghost?
Let's explore the clues
left at the scene.
現場に残されたヒントを探りましょう
What color... are you?
あなたは…　何色なの？
鹿矛囲の隠れ家には　移植用の臓器の他に
Besides transplant organs,
it looks like there were bio-contact lenses
with a traced retinal pattern
in Kamui's hideout.
網膜パターンをトレースした生体コンタクトが　置かれてたみたい
The retinal pattern
must be Mizue Shisui's.
網膜パターンは　酒々井水絵のものだな
Very perceptive.
I'm impressed you guessed it.
ご明察　よく分かったわね
In order for an unauthorized person
to use a Dominator,
適正を持たない人間が　ドミネーターを扱うには
they have no choice but to have it
falsely recognize them as authorized.
適正者であるように　誤認識させるしかない
To Kamui, she's probably a pawn
who serves that purpose, so...
鹿矛囲にとって　彼女はそのための駒だろうからな
だから　酒々井監視官の反応が　複数感知されたわけね
So that's why we detected
multiple Inspector Shisuis.
奪われたドミネーターは８丁か
Eight Dominators
have been taken, huh?
Then, from here on, up to eight
Mizue Shisuis will probably be detected.
なら　酒々井水絵の反応は　今後８人まで増えるだろうな
You sound pretty calm about this.
ずいぶん　のんきなのね
それとも　もう　止める手だてを考えてあるのかしら？
Or have you already come up
with a way to stop them?
そんなものはない
Nope, I've got nothing.
As long as Sibyl continues
to recognize her actions as valid,
シビュラが彼女の行動を正しいと認め続けるかぎり
those Dominators
will continue to be used.
ドミネーターは使われ続けるさ
Hey, is that sarcasm
towards Sibyl?
ちょっと…　シビュラに対する嫌み？
疑念だよ
No, it's suspicion.
That's even worse.
余計　悪いわよ
Imposters are just walking around
without any problems
本人ではない人間がまかり通り
and an Inspector
who's aiding a criminal is at large...
犯罪者に協力する監視官が野放し
I'm just stating the facts.
事実を言ってるだけだ
Well then, both of you,
please go back.
では　２人も引き揚げてください
I'll stay here a bit longer
and search Kamui's hideout.
私はもう少しここに残って　鹿矛囲の隠れ家を探ってみます
常守　少し休んだ方がいい
Tsunemori, you should rest a bit.
I agree.
私も賛成です
でも　あんまり休める状態じゃないんですよ　うち
But I can't really get
much rest at my apartment...
...since I've been keeping
the crime scene as is.
現場を維持したままなので
Hold on a second!
You haven't moved?! What're you thinking?!
ちょっと待て　お前　引っ越してないのか
何を考えてる！
まさか　自分を餌にするつもりですか
Don't tell me... Are you trying
to use yourself as bait?
I'm not that foolhardy.
I just haven't had time to, that's all.
そこまで　怖いもの知らずじゃないですよ
手続きする時間が　取れないだけです
あきれた
You're unbelievable...
What? Grandma's...?
おばあちゃんが？
At the nursing home
where Aoi Tsunemori is staying
保護対象　常守葵の収容介護施設にて
while in protective custody,
there was a malfunction with the nursing Drones.
養護ドローンの異常が発生
Grandma!
おばあちゃん！
What's the matter?
You look pale.
どうしたんだい？　血相　変えて
おばあちゃん…
Grandma...
It's been a while, Akane.
久しぶりだね　あーちゃん
Ms. Aoi Tsunemori
I'm so glad to see
that you're okay.
よかった　おばあちゃんに何もなくて
大げさだね　このくらいのことで　仕事ほっぽって来るなんてさ
You're overreacting.
To see you neglect your work
and come here over such a trifling matter...
Well, it's not like
I neglected my job...
いや…　別に　ほっぽって来たわけじゃ
You haven't changed at all.
そういうところ　変わらないねえ
あーちゃんは　昔から自分のこと差し置いて
You single-mindedly focus
on the needs of others instead of your own.
人のために突っ走る
ごめんね　いつも　迷惑掛けて
I'm sorry that I always
cause you trouble.
Don't be silly.
I never think you cause me trouble.
バカだね　迷惑だなんて思ってないよ
You know how valuable
peoples' lives are.
命の大切さ　重さを知っている
You must always
hold on to that, okay?
それは何があっても　絶対なくしちゃいけないよ　あーちゃん
Grandma...
おばあちゃん…
Thank you.
ありがとう
事件の概要については　報告を受けている
I've already been
briefed about the case.
I came to see you today
to hear Sibyl's thoughts.
今日　来たのは　シビュラの考えを聞くためよ
Why haven't you
taken any action
なぜ　あなたたちは酒々井監視官のドミネーターに使用停止措置を取らないの？
to deactivate the Dominator
used by Inspector Shisui?
彼女の行動は　全て　把握しているはず
I'm sure you've been
keeping tabs on all of her actions.
Of course we have.
当然だ
But Inspector Shisui's
Psycho-Pass is still clear.
しかし　酒々井監視官のサイコパスはクリアなままなのでね
There's no reason for us
to stop an Inspector
サイコパスがクリアなまま　行動している監視官を
whose Psycho-Pass
is clear from taking action.
われわれが止める理由はない
あってはいけないの間違いでしょ？
You mean you can't, because doing so
would mean the system is flawed.
それは　自己の否定に　つながるから
Watch your mouth,
Inspector Tsunemori.
口を慎みたまえ　常守監視官
既存の制約に縛られたままでは　今回の犯人は裁けない
We can't bring this culprit to justice
while being bound by the current rules.
You're talking about Kamui?
鹿矛囲か…
I've read your report.
You said the Dominators didn't even recognize him.
君の報告書は目を通した
ドミネーターが認識すらしなかったそうだね
Yes.
ええ
That's not possible.
あり得ない話だな
It's one thing if he was criminally asymptomatic.
But a person who can't
免罪体質ならいざ知らず
スキャン自体が不可能なイレギュラーなど　存在するはずがない
even be scanned?
Such an irregularity is impossible.
But the reality is that this irregularity
that can't exist has appeared.
しかし　現に存在するはずのないイレギュラーは現れた
How are we supposed to deal
with someone like that?
そんな相手に　私たちはどう対処すればいい？
簡単なことだ
It's simple. In fact,
you tried to do it, right?
現に　君は実行しようとしたのだろう？
Are you saying that
killing him is appropriate?
殺処分が適当だと？
Wasn't it a mistake for you
to stop Enforcer Togane?
東金執行官を止めたのは　誤りだったんじゃないかね？
It's strange.
不自然だわ
Sibyl System... You guys have been
maintaining the system
シビュラシステム　あなたたちは
免罪体質者というイレギュラーを　自らに取り込むことによって
by taking in irregular people
who were criminally asymptomatic.
システムを維持してきた
But when it comes to Kamui,
でも　鹿矛囲にかぎっては　観察対象にさえせずに
you're trying to eliminate him
from society without even observing him.
社会から　消し去ろうとしている
つまり　あなたたちはすでに結論を出している
In other words, you guys have
already come to a conclusion...
...that Kamui is the kind of irregularity
whom you cannot take in.
鹿矛囲の正体…
それが　自分に取り込めない種類のイレギュラーであると
You're as interesting as ever.
君は　相変わらず面白いな
Even if that was true,
what are you saying you're going to do?
仮にそうだとしたら　どうするというのだね？
I'll solve the mystery
behind Kamui without fail.
鹿矛囲の謎は必ず解き明かす
And then, we'll arrest him
and bring him to rightful justice.
その上で　私たちの手で逮捕し　正当な法の裁きを受けさせるわ
Any problem with that?
何か問題が？
No. Continue to strive
to fulfill your duty.
いいや
引き続き　職務に励みたまえ
Then, excuse me.
失礼します
取り繕った跡があるが
I can see they tried to cover it up,
but things are out of order
and they aren't
lined up properly.
順番と　上下がずれている
Akane Tsunemori
詰めが甘いな
They're not thorough, are they...?
コピーした痕跡
Looks like they made a copy.
The data they copied was...
該当するデータは…　俺の経歴か
...my background, huh?
なるほど
I see...
Well, well...
よほど　俺のことが気に入らないらしいな
You must really dislike me,
Inspector Shimotsuki.
霜月監視官
An old personnel file?
古い人事ファイル？
１８年前に一度　執行官として配属されてる
He was assigned as an Enforcer
once eighteen years ago.
He was twenty-three
years old at the time.
当時２３歳
All the Inspectors
he worked with
担当監視官は全員潜在犯落ちして
became latent criminals
and were executed with Eliminators.
エリミネーターで執行
This data wasn't
made available to us.
こんなデータ私たちの所に下りてきてない
What's with this guy?
何なの？　こいつ
So we have everyone here?
現状はこれで全員ですね
Yeah, I was told that Enforcer Sugo
won't be able to come back for a while.
ああ　須郷執行官は復帰までまだしばらくかかるそうだ
Well then, let's start.
それじゃ　始めましょう
The question for the present is how
we go after Kamui, who we lost at the port.
当座の問題は　港で消息を絶った鹿矛囲をどう追うかだな
We searched
for Representative Kotoku Masuda
接触する可能性も　あるかと
増田幸徳議員の行方を追いましたが
thinking that
he might see Kamui...
釈放後　すぐに命を絶ったようです
...but it looks like he died
right after he was released.
He chose to die
without hesitation.
迷うことなく死を選ぶ
That's how much
he admired Kamui.
それほど　心酔しているということ
We knew he wasn't the real Masuda,
and yet, we couldn't do anything.
入れ替わった人間と分かっていながら　何もできなかった
We won't let Kamui do
as he pleases anymore.
これ以上　好きにはさせません
まずは現場に残された物証から洗っていきましょう
Let's start by investigating
the evidence left at the scene.
What stood out were
the large number of organs
目立ったのは　やはり大量の臓器
as well as an enormous amount
of stress care medicine.
それと同じく　大量のストレスケアの薬ですね
Th-This is amazing.
こ…これすごい
What's amazing, Hinakawa?
何が　すごいの？　雛河君
Th-They're mostly illegal drugs
that were personally compounded.
ほ…ほとんどが独自に調合された違法薬
I've never seen
combinations like these.
こんな組み合わせ　見たことない
Also, it's impossible to adjust them
with this level of detail.
あと　ここまで細かく調節するの　無理
I don't understand.
意味分かんないんだけど
If all you're looking for is to do some
basic compounding for a simple effect,
適当な調合で　そ…それなりの効き目出すのだったら
僕でもできるけど
I can do it, too.
But if he was aiming for these results,
his knowledge is beyond average.
狙ってやってるとしたら　普通の知識じゃない
You mean, he has
an extraordinary knowledge of drugs?
薬物に関して並外れた知識がある　そういうこと？
Ah, yes.
Maybe him wearing a pharmacist's Holo
wasn't really just pretending.
薬剤師のホロまとってたのも
案外フリだけじゃないのかも
Pharmacist's Holo?
Kamui was wearing it?
薬剤師のホロ？
鹿矛囲がそれをまとってたの？
Hm? Ah, y-yes. I discovered it
when the barricade incident happened.
立てこもり事件のとき　見つけた
注意して見たら　分かった
When I looked closely,
I noticed it.
I-It was well made,
but it was a Holo.
よくできてたけど　あれ…　ホロ
Why didn't you report it?
どうして　報告しなかったの？
I-I-I sent the data
to Inspector Shimotsuki.
デ…デ…データ
霜月監視官に　お…送りました
What?
I do have a record of sending it.
送信履歴　ちゃんとある
なぜ口頭で報告しなかったんですか
Why didn't you report it verbally?!
You didn't notify me properly!
これは　あなたの伝達ミスです
Operational improvement can wait.
業務改善は後よ
Hinakawa, send the data
to the Analysis Lab.
雛河君　データを分析室に
ねえ　もしかして　これもそうだったりして
Hey, is it possible...
...that this one is the same?
ほら　やっぱり
See, I knew it. This is also a Holo
created by aging someone up.
これも成長復元ホロよ
I just tried cross-referencing it with
the children that died in that plane crash.
試しに例の航空機事故で亡くなった子供の中から検索したら
This is a perfect match.
ぴったり　一致
The plane accident
fifteen years ago...
１５年前の航空機事故
Just like the woman's Holo
used by Kamui in the first incident.
第１の事件で鹿矛囲が使っていた女性のホロと同じ
Our assumptions
were incorrect.
私たちは前提条件を間違えていた
What we need to focus on
isn't the first woman.
焦点にすべきは最初の女性じゃない
It's all the children
who died in this accident.
この事故で死んだ全ての子供たちよ
Ms. Karanomori, please check
the details of the accident.
唐之杜さん　事故の詳細を
Okay.
了解
Nikku Airlines Flight Crashes
With 205 People On Board
School Trip Tragedy. Nikku plane crashes.
事故は１５年前の５月
The crash happened
fifteen years ago in May.
A plane carrying
elementary school students on a school trip
修学旅行に向かう小学校の生徒を乗せた旅客機が
Nikku Airlines Flight 321 Crashes!
The safety of 205 passengers
and crew is currently unknown.
crashed into Mt. Kumataka.
熊鷹山に墜落した
It says the cause was
a problem with the airframe.
原因は機体トラブルとあるわね
Victims included 185 children
along with accompanying adults,
犠牲者は１８５名の子供たちに
crew members and the pilots.
A total of two hundred and two people.
引率や　乗務員　パイロットを　合わせた　２０２名
Wait!
待って　生存者が一人だけいるわ
There was one survivor.
This name...
この名前…
鹿矛囲…　桐斗
Kirito Kamui...
たった一人の生存者
He was the only survivor...!
No good. The record on Kirito Kamui
cannot be accessed
駄目ね　鹿矛囲桐斗についての記録は
even with the MWPSB's authority.
公安の権限でも閲覧不可になってる
理由は医療上の機密保持のためとなってるけど…
It says that the reason
is medical confidentiality.
Let's check into the people
involved with his surgery.
オペの関係者を当たりましょう
一番詳しそうな人は…　と
The one who seems to be
the most knowledgeable about it is...
Oh, the operating surgeon
at the time is still practicing.
あら　当時の執刀医さんが　まだ現役ね
すぐに向かいます
I'll go see him immediately.
Ms. Shimotsuki, please come with me.
霜月さんは　同行を
Okay.
了解です
Thank you, Hinakawa.
ありがとう　雛河君
Thanks to you,
we were able to find Kamui.
あなたのおかげで　鹿矛囲を見つけることができたわ
Oh... s-sure.
Please continue to work
on creating Holos of the 185 children
引き続き事故被害者の子供たち
１８５名の成長復元ホロ作成をお願いします
who were victims
of the accident by aging them up.
A-All of them?!
ぜ…全部？
Are you having
just one person do all that?
それ　１人で　やらせるんですか？
We might be able to identify
a third Holo and even a fourth one.
第３第４のホロが特定できるかもしれない
Can you do it, Hinakawa?
雛河君　できる？
I-I can, b-big sis.
や…　やれます　お…　お姉ちゃん
Ms. Kunizuka, please check
and see if there are people
六合塚さんは事故被害者と同姓同名の人物がいないか　調べてください
who share the same names
as the accident victims.
Okay.
了解しました
Mr. Ginoza, Mr. Togane.
Please use the organs we seized at his hideout
宜野座さんと東金さんは
現場で押収した臓器から　入れ替わった人物の特定を
to identify the people
who are impersonators.
Got it.
了解だ
Understood.
了解しました
I finished all the necessary preparations.
必要な処置は全て終わらせた
Once you receive them,
all of you will be able to use the Dominators.
あれが届けば君たちは全員ドミネーターを扱える
Thank you. All I have to do now
is find the location of the one
助かります
後は　この社会をこの社会たらしめている主の居場所を見つけるだけだ
who makes
this society what it is.
公安局の方が枡嵜先生に　お話を伺いたいそうなのですが
The MWPSB people are here.
They say they want to talk to you, Dr. Masuzaki.
通してくれ
Show them in.
はい
Yes sir.
Looks like they're here.
来たようだ
あなたにはホントに感謝している
I really appreciate your help.
I should be the one thanking you.
礼を言うのは私の方だ
I wish you all the best
in your plan, Kirito.
計画の成功を祈っているよ　桐斗君
枡嵜葉平さんですね
You're Mr. Yohei Masuzaki, right?
任意同行に応じていただけますか
Would you be willing
to come with us voluntarily?
I'm rather a poor talker.
私は口下手な方でね
ちゃんと鹿矛囲の福音を伝えられるか　不安だ
I'm worried that I won't be able
to properly convey Kamui's gospel.
Ms. Shimotsuki, once we're back,
please check Kamui's treatment record.
霜月さん　戻ったら鹿矛囲の治療記録の調査をお願い
Is that necessary?
それ必要なことですか
Since we have a witness, we just need
to get the answers through interrogation.
証言者を確保したんだから　聴取で聞き出せば済むことです
If he gets Kamui's help
to maintain a clear Psycho-Pass, too,
彼も鹿矛囲の手でサイコパスをクリアにされているなら
he might lie
in the interrogation.
聴取で偽りを述べるかもしれない
We need to corroborate his story.
裏を取る必要があるわ
Ms. Kunizuka, there's something
I want you to help me... with...
六合塚さん　手伝ってほしいことがあるんで…
…けど
I guess you'll do.
Give me a hand.
あんたでいいわ　手を貸しなさい
He suffered serious depression
もともとは重度のうつ病で
and so he became
dependent on medication.
おかげで　薬が手放せない体質に　なっちゃったと
Sho Hinakawa
Enforcer, Criminal Investigation Department Division 1
Poor thing.
かわいそうにね
He improved his skills
to protect himself,
自衛のために磨いた技術が功を奏して
which helped him become a Holo designer.
How cute, that's just like him.
ホロデザイナーに　なってるとこなんて
彼らしくて　カワイイわ
If that was the whole story,
he didn't have to become an Enforcer.
それだけで済んでいれば執行官になることもなかったのに
手術記録の閲覧レベル　すごく高い設定にされてる　何で
The authorization level for the surgery records
is set quite high. Why?
How should I know?
I'll leave the rest to you.
知らないわよ　後は任せたわ
One possibility is... that it involved
patents for technologies or drugs.
考えられるのは技術…
もしくは　薬剤特許を取得するため
Drug patents...
薬剤特許？
One of the leading organizations
with drug patents in Japan is...
日本有数の薬剤特許取得団体
その名義は確か…
...if I remember correctly...
...the Togane Foundation.
東金財団
On second thought,
I'll investigate this case.
やっぱりこの件は私が調べます
You work on creating
the aged up Holos.
雛河は成長復元ホロの作成を
Those were
Inspector Tsunemori's orders, right?
先輩からの命令でしょ
G-Got it.
りょ…了解
May I ask you
to interrogate him, Mr. Saiga?
お願いできますか　先生
I don't think there'll be much need
for interrogation this time.
お願いされるような　ことは何もないさ
He's planning
to tell us everything. Right?
こいつは全部話すつもりだ
そうだろ？
誰でもいいわけではありませんよ
I won't talk to just anyone.
But fortunately, it seems that
you're wise and trustworthy.
しかし　幸いにもあなたは聡明で信用に足る人物のようだ
Thanks.
ありがとよ
I'll tell you about Kamui.
お話ししましょう　鹿矛囲のことを
Sho's just sent me an email saying that
he finished with the 185 aged up Holos.
今翔君からメールが届いたわ
１８５人分の成長復元ホロできたって
He's...!
彼は…
This guy is...
こいつは…
軍事ドローン施設のプログラマー
...the programmer
at the Military Drone facility.
I remember seeing
some others, too.
他にも見覚えがある
That guy was, if I remember right,
in charge of vehicle maintenance.
あいつは確か車両のメンテナンス係だったはず
You probably think that one single guy,
Kamui, has been making fools of you.
あなた方は鹿矛囲桐斗一人にいいように翻弄されていると思っていませんか
But that's wrong.
He was never alone at all.
だが　それは違う
彼はそもそも１人ではない
第３第４のホロどころじゃない
Forget the third
or the fourth Holo.
Kamui... has been
right beside us all this time.
鹿矛囲は
ずっと　私たちのそばに　いた
All is calm, all is bright
All is calm All is bright
A whispering fallen angel
Sasayaku tenshi wa ochite
囁く天使は堕ちて
Gently devours you, body and soul
Yasashiku hamu wa anata no subete o
優しく食むわ　あなたの全てを
It's my guilty
You notice me
Kidzuku
気づく　目を見開いてる
With your eyes wide open,
Me o mihiraiteru
A faint blue as lifeless as concrete
Honoaoi konkuriito
仄青い混凝土
In a cold tone,
Tsumetaku watashi o
冷たく私を
Call my name and give me a kiss
And then hold me in the arms of the empty shell that is your body
Soshite dakishimete anata no inai sono karada de
そして抱きしめて
あなたのいないその体で
That soul that you've cast out
Hakidashita sono inochi wa
吐き出しその生命は
Has not yet completely vanished
Mada katachi o nokoshiteiru wa
まだ形を残しているわ　紅く
I glimpse a vivid red eternity
Akaku azayaka na eien ga miete
鮮やかな永遠が見えて
It starts singing right next to me
Tonari de sore wa utaidasu
隣でそれは歌いだすわ
What was I born for
Come on, love me
Nee watashi o aishite
ねえ　私を愛して
Because I won't let you go
Hanasanai kara
離さないから
Hello my name is
A world where humans' state of mind
and the tendency of their personalities can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls
are commonly called 'Psycho-Pass.'
This story is fiction.
The names of all individuals and organizations
that appear in the show are fictitious,
and have no relation to those in existence in the real world.